{
  "hiraSeion": [
    { "question": "あ", "answer": "a" },
    { "question": "い", "answer": "i" },
    { "question": "う", "answer": "u" },
    { "question": "え", "answer": "e" },
    { "question": "お", "answer": "o" },
    { "question": "か", "answer": "ka" },
    { "question": "き", "answer": "ki" },
    { "question": "く", "answer": "ku" },
    { "question": "け", "answer": "ke" },
    { "question": "こ", "answer": "ko" },
    { "question": "さ", "answer": "sa" },
    { "question": "し", "answer": ["si", "shi"] },
    { "question": "す", "answer": "su" },
    { "question": "せ", "answer": "se" },
    { "question": "そ", "answer": "so" },
    { "question": "た", "answer": "ta" },
    { "question": "ち", "answer": ["ti", "chi"] },
    { "question": "つ", "answer": ["tu", "tsu"] },
    { "question": "て", "answer": "te" },
    { "question": "と", "answer": "to" },
    { "question": "な", "answer": "na" },
    { "question": "に", "answer": "ni" },
    { "question": "ぬ", "answer": "nu" },
    { "question": "ね", "answer": "ne" },
    { "question": "の", "answer": "no" },
    { "question": "は", "answer": "ha" },
    { "question": "ひ", "answer": "hi" },
    { "question": "ふ", "answer": ["hu", "fu"] },
    { "question": "へ", "answer": "he" },
    { "question": "ほ", "answer": "ho" },
    { "question": "ま", "answer": "ma" },
    { "question": "み", "answer": "mi" },
    { "question": "む", "answer": "mu" },
    { "question": "め", "answer": "me" },
    { "question": "も", "answer": "mo" },
    { "question": "や", "answer": "ya" },
    { "question": "ゆ", "answer": "yu" },
    { "question": "よ", "answer": "yo" },
    { "question": "ら", "answer": "ra" },
    { "question": "り", "answer": "ri" },
    { "question": "る", "answer": "ru" },
    { "question": "れ", "answer": "re" },
    { "question": "ろ", "answer": "ro" },
    { "question": "わ", "answer": "wa" },
    { "question": "を", "answer": "wo" },
    { "question": "ん", "answer": "n" }
  ],
  "hiraDakuon": [
    { "question": "が", "answer": "ga" },
    { "question": "ぎ", "answer": "gi" },
    { "question": "ぐ", "answer": "gu" },
    { "question": "げ", "answer": "ge" },
    { "question": "ご", "answer": "go" },
    { "question": "ざ", "answer": "za" },
    { "question": "じ", "answer": "ji" },
    { "question": "ず", "answer": "zu" },
    { "question": "ぜ", "answer": "ze" },
    { "question": "ぞ", "answer": "zo" },
    { "question": "だ", "answer": "da" },
    { "question": "ぢ", "answer": "ji" },
    { "question": "づ", "answer": "zu" },
    { "question": "で", "answer": "de" },
    { "question": "ど", "answer": "do" },
    { "question": "ば", "answer": "ba" },
    { "question": "び", "answer": "bi" },
    { "question": "ぶ", "answer": "bu" },
    { "question": "べ", "answer": "be" },
    { "question": "ぼ", "answer": "bo" }
  ],
  "hiraHandakuon": [
    { "question": "ぱ", "answer": "pa" },
    { "question": "ぴ", "answer": "pi" },
    { "question": "ぷ", "answer": "pu" },
    { "question": "ぺ", "answer": "pe" },
    { "question": "ぽ", "answer": "po" }
  ],
  "hiraYouon": [
    { "question": "きゃ", "answer": "kya" },
    { "question": "きゅ", "answer": "kyu" },
    { "question": "きょ", "answer": "kyo" },
    { "question": "しゃ", "answer": "sha" },
    { "question": "しゅ", "answer": "shu" },
    { "question": "しょ", "answer": "sho" },
    { "question": "ちゃ", "answer": "cha" },
    { "question": "ちゅ", "answer": "chu" },
    { "question": "ちょ", "answer": "cho" },
    { "question": "にゃ", "answer": "nya" },
    { "question": "にゅ", "answer": "nyu" },
    { "question": "にょ", "answer": "nyo" },
    { "question": "ひゃ", "answer": "hya" },
    { "question": "ひゅ", "answer": "hyu" },
    { "question": "ひょ", "answer": "hyo" },
    { "question": "みゃ", "answer": "mya" },
    { "question": "みゅ", "answer": "myu" },
    { "question": "みょ", "answer": "myo" },
    { "question": "りゃ", "answer": "rya" },
    { "question": "りゅ", "answer": "ryu" },
    { "question": "りょ", "answer": "ryo" },
    { "question": "ぎゃ", "answer": "gya" },
    { "question": "ぎゅ", "answer": "gyu" },
    { "question": "ぎょ", "answer": "gyo" },
    { "question": "じゃ", "answer": "ja" },
    { "question": "じゅ", "answer": "ju" },
    { "question": "じょ", "answer": "jo" },
    { "question": "びゃ", "answer": "bya" },
    { "question": "びゅ", "answer": "byu" },
    { "question": "びょ", "answer": "byo" },
    { "question": "ぴゃ", "answer": "pya" },
    { "question": "ぴゅ", "answer": "pyu" },
    { "question": "ぴょ", "answer": "pyo" }
  ],
  "kataSeion": [
    { "question": "ア", "answer": "a" },
    { "question": "イ", "answer": "i" },
    { "question": "ウ", "answer": "u" },
    { "question": "エ", "answer": "e" },
    { "question": "オ", "answer": "o" },
    { "question": "カ", "answer": "ka" },
    { "question": "キ", "answer": "ki" },
    { "question": "ク", "answer": "ku" },
    { "question": "ケ", "answer": "ke" },
    { "question": "コ", "answer": "ko" },
    { "question": "サ", "answer": "sa" },
    { "question": "シ", "answer": ["si", "shi"] },
    { "question": "ス", "answer": "su" },
    { "question": "セ", "answer": "se" },
    { "question": "ソ", "answer": "so" },
    { "question": "タ", "answer": "ta" },
    { "question": "チ", "answer": ["ti", "chi"] },
    { "question": "ツ", "answer": ["tu", "tsu"] },
    { "question": "テ", "answer": "te" },
    { "question": "ト", "answer": "to" },
    { "question": "ナ", "answer": "na" },
    { "question": "ニ", "answer": "ni" },
    { "question": "ヌ", "answer": "nu" },
    { "question": "ネ", "answer": "ne" },
    { "question": "ノ", "answer": "no" },
    { "question": "ハ", "answer": "ha" },
    { "question": "ヒ", "answer": "hi" },
    { "question": "フ", "answer": ["hu", "fu"] },
    { "question": "ヘ", "answer": "he" },
    { "question": "ホ", "answer": "ho" },
    { "question": "マ", "answer": "ma" },
    { "question": "ミ", "answer": "mi" },
    { "question": "ム", "answer": "mu" },
    { "question": "メ", "answer": "me" },
    { "question": "モ", "answer": "mo" },
    { "question": "ヤ", "answer": "ya" },
    { "question": "ユ", "answer": "yu" },
    { "question": "ヨ", "answer": "yo" },
    { "question": "ラ", "answer": "ra" },
    { "question": "リ", "answer": "ri" },
    { "question": "ル", "answer": "ru" },
    { "question": "レ", "answer": "re" },
    { "question": "ロ", "answer": "ro" },
    { "question": "ワ", "answer": "wa" },
    { "question": "ヲ", "answer": "wo" },
    { "question": "ン", "answer": "n" }
  ],
  "kataDakuon": [
    { "question": "ガ", "answer": "ga" },
    { "question": "ギ", "answer": "gi" },
    { "question": "グ", "answer": "gu" },
    { "question": "ゲ", "answer": "ge" },
    { "question": "ゴ", "answer": "go" },
    { "question": "ザ", "answer": "za" },
    { "question": "ジ", "answer": "ji" },
    { "question": "ズ", "answer": "zu" },
    { "question": "ゼ", "answer": "ze" },
    { "question": "ゾ", "answer": "zo" },
    { "question": "ダ", "answer": "da" },
    { "question": "ヂ", "answer": "ji" },
    { "question": "ヅ", "answer": "zu" },
    { "question": "デ", "answer": "de" },
    { "question": "ド", "answer": "do" },
    { "question": "バ", "answer": "ba" },
    { "question": "ビ", "answer": "bi" },
    { "question": "ブ", "answer": "bu" },
    { "question": "ベ", "answer": "be" },
    { "question": "ボ", "answer": "bo" }
  ],
  "kataHandakuon": [
    { "question": "パ", "answer": "pa" },
    { "question": "ピ", "answer": "pi" },
    { "question": "プ", "answer": "pu" },
    { "question": "ペ", "answer": "pe" },
    { "question": "ポ", "answer": "po" }
  ],
  "kataYouon": [
    { "question": "キャ", "answer": "kya" },
    { "question": "キュ", "answer": "kyu" },
    { "question": "キョ", "answer": "kyo" },
    { "question": "シャ", "answer": "sha" },
    { "question": "シュ", "answer": "shu" },
    { "question": "ショ", "answer": "sho" },
    { "question": "チャ", "answer": "cha" },
    { "question": "チュ", "answer": "chu" },
    { "question": "チョ", "answer": "cho" },
    { "question": "ニャ", "answer": "nya" },
    { "question": "ニュ", "answer": "nyu" },
    { "question": "ニョ", "answer": "nyo" },
    { "question": "ヒャ", "answer": "hya" },
    { "question": "ヒュ", "answer": "hyu" },
    { "question": "ヒョ", "answer": "hyo" },
    { "question": "ミャ", "answer": "mya" },
    { "question": "ミュ", "answer": "myu" },
    { "question": "ミョ", "answer": "myo" },
    { "question": "リャ", "answer": "rya" },
    { "question": "リュ", "answer": "ryu" },
    { "question": "リョ", "answer": "ryo" },
    { "question": "ギャ", "answer": "gya" },
    { "question": "ギュ", "answer": "gyu" },
    { "question": "ギョ", "answer": "gyo" },
    { "question": "ジャ", "answer": "ja" },
    { "question": "ジュ", "answer": "ju" },
    { "question": "ジョ", "answer": "jo" },
    { "question": "ビャ", "answer": "bya" },
    { "question": "ビュ", "answer": "byu" },
    { "question": "ビョ", "answer": "byo" },
    { "question": "ピャ", "answer": "pya" },
    { "question": "ピュ", "answer": "pyu" },
    { "question": "ピョ", "answer": "pyo" }
  ]
}
